Guide to the James Beard Foundation Archive 1939-2008 (bulk 1990-2008) MSS.214
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Food Writers and Personalities
  - Jaffe, Matthew, undated (Box 54, Folder 70)
  - Jaffrey, Madur, undated (Box 54, Folder 71)
  - Jamison, Bill and Cheryl, undated (Box 54, Folder 72)
  - Jaret, Peter, undated (Box 54, Folder 73)
  - Jefferson, Thomas, undated (Box 54, Folder 74)
  - Jenkins, Emyl, undated (Box 54, Folder 75)
  - Jenkins, Nancy Harmon, undated (Box 54, Folder 76)
  - Jenkins, Steven, undated (Box 54, Folder 77)
  - Johns, Paula Sheldon, undated (Box 54, Folder 78)
  - Johnson, Hugh, undated (Box 54, Folder 79)
  - Johnson, Peter, undated (Box 54, Folder 80)
  - Johnson, Tim, undated (Box 54, Folder 81)
  - Jones, Evan, undated (Box 54, Folder 82)
  - Jones, Jeanne, undated (Box 54, Folder 83)
  - Jue, Joyce, undated (Box 54, Folder 84)
  - Jones, Judith Ann, undated (Box 54, Folder 85)
  - Julian, Sheryl, undated (Box 54, Folder 86)
  - Juran, Sylvia, undated (Box 54, Folder 87)
  - Kafka, Barbara, undated (Box 54, Folder 88)
  - Kamman, Madeline, undated (Box 54, Folder 89)
  - Kaplan, Sherman, undated (Box 54, Folder 90)
  - Karmel, Elizabeth, undated (Box 54, Folder 91)
  - Kasper, Lynn Rosetto, undated (Box 54, Folder 92)
  - Katalinich, Peggy, undated (Box 54, Folder 93)
  - Kelly, Marcia, undated (Box 54, Folder 94)
  - Kennedy, Diana, undated (Box 54, Folder 95)
  - Kerr, Graham, undated (Box 54, Folder 96)
  - Kerr, W. Park, undated (Box 54, Folder 97)
  - Kimball, Christopher, undated (Box 54, Folder 98)
  - King, Shirley, undated (Box 54, Folder 99)
  - King, Shirley, undated (Box 54, Folder 100)
  - Kinney, Pat, undated (Box 54, Folder 101)
  - Kirkman, Tom, undated (Box 54, Folder 102)
  - Klavan, Ellen, undated (Box 54, Folder 103)
  - Kleinman, Kathryn, undated (Box 54, Folder 104)
  - Knickerbocker, Peggy, undated (Box 54, Folder 105)
  - Knight, Steve, undated (Box 54, Folder 106)
  - Kochilas, Diane, undated (Box 54, Folder 107)
  - Koplan, Steven, undated (Box 54, Folder 108)
  - Kosaka, Melanie, undated (Box 54, Folder 109)
  - Kummer, Corby, undated (Box 54, Folder 110)
  - Kump, Peter (1 of 2), undated (Box 54, Folder 111)
  - Kump, Peter (2 of 2), undated (Box 54, Folder 112)
  - Kurtz, Swoosie, undated (Box 54, Folder 113)
  - Lacalamita, Tom, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - La France, Peter, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Lahiri, Jhumpa, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Lakshmi, Padma, undated (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Lasher, Joan, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Laube, James, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Laursen, Theresa Volpe and Byron, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Leach, Robin, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Leaf, Alexandra, undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Leahy, Donna, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Lemlin, Jeanne, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Lesem, Jeanne, undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Levine, Ed, undated (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Levy, Paul, undated (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Lieberman, Trudy, undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Light, Luise, undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Livingston, Cecilia, undated (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Loha-unchit, Kasma, undated (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - London, Mel and Sheryl, undated (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Longone, Jan, undated (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Louie, Elaine, undated (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Lucas, Dione, undated (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Luchetti, Cathy, undated (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Lukins, Sheila, undated (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - McCarthy, Edward, undated (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - McCullough, Frances, undated (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - McCully, Helen, undated (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - McGee, Harold, undated (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - McMahon, Hugh, undated (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Madison, Deborah, undated (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Mattson, Robin, undated (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Marks, Copeland, undated (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Marks, Gil, undated (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Marshall, Anne, undated (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Marshall, Lydie, undated (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Masamuto, David Mas, undated (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Mather, Robin, undated (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Mayer, Caroline, undated (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Mayer, Nancy and Naomi Kaufman, undated (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Maytag, Fritz, undated (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Medrich, Alice, undated (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Mendleson, Anne, undated (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Merchant, Ismail, undated (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Millar, Heather, undated (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Miller, Bryan, undated (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Miller, Eileen, undated (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Miller, Joni, undated (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Miller, Marcin, undated (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Milza, Jane, undated (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Moosewood Collective, undated (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Mulligan, Mary Ewing, undated (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Myers, Benjamin, undated (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Myers, Perla, undated (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Moore, David, undated (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Mills, Ami Chen, undated (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Mizner, Anita, undated (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Montant, Jane, undated (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - Morash, Marian, undated (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - Morgan, Pamela, undated (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - Moulton, Sara, undated (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - Mount, Charles Morris, undated (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Murray, Janis, undated (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Nalley, Richard, undated (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Namedorf, Arthur, undated (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - Nathan, Joan, undated (Box 55, Folder 65)
  - Neal, Bill, undated (Box 55, Folder 66)
  - New Yorker Event, undated (Box 55, Folder 67)
  - Nimtz, Sharon Paquette, undated (Box 55, Folder 68)
  - Norman, Dr. Remington, undated (Box 55, Folder 69)
  - Nowlan, Mary Hearty, undated (Box 55, Folder 70)
  - Ochoa, Laurie, undated (Box 55, Folder 71)
  - Ojakangas, Beatrice, undated (Box 55, Folder 72)
  - Olney, Richard, undated (Box 55, Folder 73)
  - O'Neil, Carolyn, undated (Box 55, Folder 74)
  - O'Neil, Molly, undated (Box 55, Folder 75)
  - Oster, Maggie, undated (Box 55, Folder 76)
  - Owen, Sri, undated (Box 55, Folder 77)
  - Page, Karen, undated (Box 55, Folder 78)
  - Parker, Robert, undated (Box 55, Folder 79)
  - Parsons, Russ, undated (Box 55, Folder 80)
  - Patraker, Joel, undated (Box 55, Folder 81)
  - Payne, Rolce Redard, undated (Box 55, Folder 82)
  - Pellegrini, Angelo, undated (Box 55, Folder 83)
  - Perry, Kathleen, undated (Box 55, Folder 84)
  - Peterson, James, undated (Box 55, Folder 85)
  - Pickell, Len, undated (Box 55, Folder 86)
  - Plimpton, George, undated (Box 55, Folder 87)
  - Plotkin, Fred, undated (Box 55, Folder 88)
  - Plutt, Mary Jo, undated (Box 55, Folder 89)
  - Podell, Susan Kagen, undated (Box 55, Folder 90)
  - Polini, Bonnie Sanders, undated (Box 55, Folder 91)
  - Pratt, Steven M., undated (Box 55, Folder 92)
  - Prial, Frank, undated (Box 55, Folder 93)
  - Puzo, Daniel P., undated (Box 55, Folder 94)
  - Purdy, Susan G., undated (Box 55, Folder 95)
  - Rada, George, undated (Box 55, Folder 96)
  - Rafer, Suzanne, undated (Box 55, Folder 97)
  - Raichlen, Steven, undated (Box 55, Folder 98)
  - Rait, Stephen, undated (Box 55, Folder 99)
  - Ratner, Elaine, undated (Box 55, Folder 100)
  - Rattlez Lewis, Sandra, undated (Box 55, Folder 101)
  - Razdic, Dino, undated (Box 55, Folder 102)
  - Reichl, Ruth, undated (Box 55, Folder 103)
  - Rhulman, Michael, undated (Box 55, Folder 104)
  - Richardson, Rosamond, undated (Box 55, Folder 105)
  - Richman, Alan, undated (Box 55, Folder 106)
  - Richman, Phyllis, undated (Box 55, Folder 107)
  - Ricketts, David, undated (Box 55, Folder 108)
  - Ring, Nancy, undated (Box 55, Folder 109)
  - Risley, Mary S., undated (Box 55, Folder 110)
  - Ritter, John, undated (Box 55, Folder 111)
  - Rivera, Guadalupe, undated (Box 55, Folder 112)
  - Robinson, Jancis, undated (Box 55, Folder 113)
  - Rockwell, David, undated (Box 55, Folder 114)
  - Roden, Claudia, undated (Box 55, Folder 115)
  - Rodgers, Rick, undated (Box 55, Folder 116)
  - Roker, Al, undated (Box 55, Folder 117)
  - Rombauer, Irma S., undated (Box 55, Folder 118)
  - Roof Winner, Dee, undated (Box 55, Folder 119)
  - Rosenberg, Judy, undated (Box 55, Folder 120)
  - Rosenblum, Mort, undated (Box 55, Folder 121)
  - Rosengarten, David, undated (Box 55, Folder 122)
  - Rosin, Arielle, [undated] (Box 55, Folder 122a, Box data_value_missing_d04ca7182c6a0ece316a1e5a228477b8)
  - Rosin, Elizabeth, undated (Box 55, Folder 123)
  - Ross, David, undated (Box 55, Folder 124)
  - Rossant, Colette, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Rosso, Julie, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Routhier, Nicole, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Royal, Earnest, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Ruselli, Lynn, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Ryan, Lawrence Timothy, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Sagon, Candy, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Sahni, Julie, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - St. John, Jill, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - St. John, William, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Sandison, Teri, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Sass, Lorna, undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Sax, Irene, undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Sax, Richard, undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Sbrocco, Leslie, undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Schinz, Marina, undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Schneider, Elizabeth, undated (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Schneider, Sally, undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Schroener, Dieter, undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Schrambling, Regina, undated (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Schudel, Matt W., undated (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Schultz, Philip S., undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Schwartz, Arthur, undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Scott, Peggy Lee, undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Scott, Sally Anne, undated (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Severson, Kim, undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Shanken, Marvin, undated (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Shapiro, Laura, undated (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Shaw, David, undated (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Shaw, Marjorie, undated (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Sheehan, Jackie, undated (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Sheraton, Mimi, undated (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Shore, Bill, undated (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Short, Bobby, undated (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Silva, Reis Pedro, undated (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Simmons, Amelia, undated (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Simmons, Marie, undated (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Sims-Bell, Barbara, undated (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Smith, Barbara, undated (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Snow, Jane, undated (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Sodsook, Victor, undated (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Sohn, Dr. Mark F., undated (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Sokolov, Raymond, undated (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Sonnefeld, Albert, undated (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Sorosky, Marlene, undated (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Spieler, Marlena, undated (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Stacey, Michelle, undated (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Stallworth, Lyn, undated (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Stein, Peter J., undated (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - Stein, Richard, undated (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Stein, Wynelle and David Hirsh (Moosewood Collective), undated (Box 56, Folder 51)
  - Steingarten, Jeffrey, undated (Box 56, Folder 52)
  - Stern, Michael and Jane, undated (Box 56, Folder 53)
  - Stewart, Martha, undated (Box 56, Folder 54)
  - Stillman, Alan, undated (Box 56, Folder 55)
  - Stinchecum, Amanda Mayer, undated (Box 56, Folder 56)
  - Stock, Melissa, undated (Box 56, Folder 57)
  - Stone, Sally and Martin, undated (Box 56, Folder 58)
  - Stuart, Caroline, undated (Box 56, Folder 59)
  - Stucchi, Emanuela, undated (Box 56, Folder 60)
  - Stuck, Susan, undated (Box 56, Folder 61)
  - Studley, Helen, undated (Box 56, Folder 62)
  - Sugarman, Carole, undated (Box 56, Folder 63)
  - Susskind, Jonathan, undated (Box 56, Folder 64)
  - Swoboda, Cheri, undated (Box 56, Folder 65)
  - Temple, Lou Jane, undated (Box 56, Folder 66)
  - Thomas, Anna, undated (Box 56, Folder 67)
  - Thompson, Jennifer Trainer, undated (Box 56, Folder 68)
  - Thompson, Sylvia, undated (Box 56, Folder 69)
  - Tibbetts, Jean, undated (Box 56, Folder 70)
  - Tihany, Adam, undated (Box 56, Folder 71)
  - Tolley, Emilie, undated (Box 56, Folder 72)
  - Tolley, Lynne, undated (Box 56, Folder 73)
  - Trager, James, undated (Box 56, Folder 74)
  - Trainer, Jennifer, undated (Box 56, Folder 75)
  - Trang, Corrine, undated (Box 56, Folder 76)
  - Trillin, Calvin, undated (Box 56, Folder 77)
  - Triplette, Clay, undated (Box 56, Folder 78)
  - Tropp, Barbara, undated (Box 56, Folder 79)
  - True, Margo, undated (Box 56, Folder 80)
  - Tunnell, Lisa, undated (Box 56, Folder 81)
  - Ujlaki, Tina, undated (Box 56, Folder 82)
  - Unterman, Patricia, undated (Box 56, Folder 83)
  - Usher, Gregory, undated (Box 56, Folder 84)
  - Valle, Victor and Mary Lou, undated (Box 56, Folder 85)
  - Van Cleave, Jill, undated (Box 56, Folder 86)
  - Van Waerbeck, Ruth, undated (Box 56, Folder 87)
  - Vaughn, John, undated (Box 56, Folder 88)
  - Verde Barr, Nancy, undated (Box 56, Folder 89)
  - Versteeg, Nicolass, undated (Box 56, Folder 90)
  - Villas, James, undated (Box 56, Folder 91)
  - Voltz, Jeanne, undated (Box 56, Folder 92)
  - Von Bremzen, Anya, undated (Box 56, Folder 93)
  - Waldron, Maggie, undated (Box 56, Folder 94)
  - Walsh, Robb, undated (Box 56, Folder 95)
  - Ware, Bradley, undated (Box 56, Folder 96)
  - Warner, Joie, undated (Box 56, Folder 97)
  - Wasserstein, Wendy, undated (Box 56, Folder 98)
  - Waters, Christina, undated (Box 56, Folder 99)
  - Waxman, Nach, undated (Box 56, Folder 100)
  - Weaver, William Woys, undated (Box 56, Folder 101)
  - Weinstein, Norman, undated (Box 56, Folder 102)
  - Weir, Joanne, undated (Box 56, Folder 103)
  - Wells, Patricia, undated (Box 56, Folder 104)
  - Welzel, Karin A., undated (Box 56, Folder 105)
  - Westmoreland, Susan, undated (Box 56, Folder 106)
  - Wheaton, Dennis Ray, undated (Box 56, Folder 107a)
  - Wilber, Susan, undated (Box 56, Folder 107b)
  - Wicks, Judy, [undated] (Box 56, Folder 107c, Box data_value_missing_f872b3d481ad7bbe6994b9c7db41750b)
  - Willan, Anne, undated (Box 56, Folder 108)
  - Williams, Chuck, undated (Box 56, Folder 109)
  - Willoughsby, John, undated (Box 56, Folder 110)
  - Wilson, Julie, undated (Box 56, Folder 111)
  - Witt, Barbara, undated (Box 56, Folder 112)
  - Witty, Helen, undated (Box 56, Folder 113)
  - Wolf, Burt, undated (Box 56, Folder 114)
  - Wolf, Clark, undated (Box 56, Folder 115)
  - Woljert, Paula, undated (Box 56, Folder 116)
  - Wynna, Dan, undated (Box 56, Folder 117)
  - Yan, Martin, undated (Box 56, Folder 118)
  - Yin Fei Lo, Eileen, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Zagat, Tim and Linda, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Zaslavsky, Nancy, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Zee, A, Undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Zimmerman, Linda, Undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Zraly, Kevin, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Series III: Food Writers and Personalities (flat box)
  - Chalmers, Irena, October 1994 (Box 58, Folder 8, Box data_value_missing_00b703ad0caa91bb9684004bce7ecd11)
  - Coe, Sophie, June 9, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 9, Box data_value_missing_99d0fafe16a01a3a823a31f4783be7ca)
  - Cunningham, Manon, April 1992 (Box 58, Folder 10, Box data_value_missing_85c6966ddbc11c6c2d5eabb6cb751354)
  - Daley, Rosie, May 25, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 11, Box data_value_missing_e5fa1c046f5e315415cfba93983c0b65)
  - Fisher, MFK, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 12, Box data_value_missing_002684e03d034d29441fb9a363a390f9)
  - Fitch, Noel Riley, September 23, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 13, Box data_value_missing_ad2e27e2551d0da4462c9ab8c064ecd4)
  - Florence, Tyler, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 14, Box data_value_missing_28a1a82166463048a843de4ada0c0eb0)
  - Fobel, Jim, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 15, Box data_value_missing_e9057ddc269181082ad61515359ba370)
  - Franey, Pierre, 9/15/1994 (Box 58, Folder 16, Box data_value_missing_6e0ac758e8281e748e66abb46a1886bd)
  - Hoppin' John, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 17, Box data_value_missing_58fa1ea7ee451ff358d95d9794501e7f)
  - Hutson, Lucinda, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 18, Box data_value_missing_07a4c189ce4fd940564c2e6a40b57e24)
  - Jackson, Michael, April 20, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 19, Box data_value_missing_519aa63a28a641ee4b7804342ce1977d)
  - Kamman, Madeleine, November 15, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 20, Box data_value_missing_e0c96ae9f63197559675e7f0cfa16533)
  - Kennedy, Diana, April 27, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 21, Box data_value_missing_9676bb469047fc5131ae1c1c80d58638)
  - Kerr, Graham, March 1994 (Box 58, Folder 22, Box data_value_missing_b5f0ef9212ab94748789c8616d81a32a)
  - Kump, Peter, January 1995 (Box 58, Folder 23, Box data_value_missing_f17c52d538ee36e5503839371ba98bf9)
  - Lacalamita, Tom, April 1994 (Box 58, Folder 24, Box data_value_missing_ac5ca66efe55f2ad4433fed9d4c755bb)
  - Lucas, Dione, April 13, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 25, Box data_value_missing_028138e2ea4fcc7903dce2ef4f634448)
  - Lukins, Sheila, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 26, Box data_value_missing_790f3f09f9be25a4f343a13f5256c8e9)
  - McMahon, Hugh, July 2, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 27, Box data_value_missing_9e990da3f954a87ac032fbfb4c379655)
  - Miller, Marcin [Whiskey Magazine], [undated] (Box 58, Folder 28, Box data_value_missing_669234e15b0c16fd2929ad9aceb42196)
  - Morse, Kitty, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 29, Box data_value_missing_193dc846599e6b4bf0e56487cb8afe0e)
  - Ring, Nancy, December 13, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 30, Box data_value_missing_ba5e9a3432b6fa4df5c037cd660aae1a)
  - Roth, David, February 4, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 31, Box data_value_missing_d09ed8383336a9e1ce212df6d711a373)
  - Rothier, Nicole, December 20, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 32, Box data_value_missing_dee880c4311ea7e3b1a1fbff00897fe9)
  - Smith, Andrew F. "Mr. Tomato", [undated] (Box 58, Folder 33, Box data_value_missing_a6180e79a918136241dcad2a1a1ef94b)
  - Sugarman, Carole, January 12, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 34, Box data_value_missing_f8046d54f3a180fe9fa52997b34b95fd)
  - Tihany, Adam, March 1, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 35, Box data_value_missing_e1f4d4c66bee929a2a2384277fdd2c36)
  - Trainer, Jennifer, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 36, Box data_value_missing_b63a805c5d0965b6e4d68a689d0225ac)
  - Unterman, Patricia, February, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 37, Box data_value_missing_a87ca1984249cc421b34692b90a3126e)
  - Urvater, Michele, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 38, Box data_value_missing_42e3e2eebced0a64ed975d6b04d492f8)
  - van Waerebeek, Ruth, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 39, Box data_value_missing_a3f1d1a36b91ff854dc11e3b48bb63c3)
  - Williams, Chuck, August 10, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 40, Box data_value_missing_88c5743eec6fb78dd6319d9907dc50c5)
  - Zagat, Tim and Nina, August 10, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 41, Box data_value_missing_ab919481a33b907f5ed0fe540e374171)
- Series IV: Miscellaneous
  - Belgian Beer, Undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - British Columbia, Prairies, Canada, Undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Meat, Undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Carnevale, Undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Celebrating Beard's Birthplace, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Chinese New Year, Undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Crawfish, Undated (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Crayfish / Sweden, 2001-2005 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Day of the Dead, Undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Dinner of the Decade, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Gingerbread, Undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Mexican Independence, Undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Mushrooms, Undated (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Mussels, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Olive Oil, Undated (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Ontario, Canada, Undated (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Persian New Year, Undated (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Pumpkin Carving, Undated (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Quebec, Undated (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Salt, September 19, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 26a, Box data_value_missing_711ec3ff240c87c5dab0f52cde4538a2)
  - Sini Fulvi [Cheese], April 8, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 26b, Box data_value_missing_b16a5b1b4d5aeee883ea8e36289616e6)
  - St. Patrick's Day, Undated (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Tet - Vietnamese New Year, Undated (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Three Kings Day, Undated (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Truffles, Undated (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Unidentified (photo of chef and drawing of restaurant), Undated (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Wasabi, Undated (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Venison (Cervena Council), Undated (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Verjus, Undated (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Venetian Carnivale, Undated (Box 60, Folder 35)
- Series IV: Miscellaneous (flat box)
  - Atlantic, Canada, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 42, Box data_value_missing_feacb0f7f01bdc6a55249d95de4d2fdb)
  - Persian New Year, March 17, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 43, Box data_value_missing_fbec261d93389633e8f48109d9b3fe33)
  - Quebec, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 44, Box data_value_missing_9f3a1d59f3995ccbc839e75348323fe5)
  - Truffles, [undated] (Box 58, Folder 45, Box data_value_missing_2eeccf76405e1e03c293c8683190eb4a)
- Oversize: Series I
  - Burgess, Linda, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Lanza, Anna Tasca, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - McLaughlin, Michael, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Meyers, Perla, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Upshur, Greg, December 1998, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Van Cleave, Jill, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Walter, Carole, October 30, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Webster, Scott, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Weldon, Douglas, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Oversize: Series II: Wine
  - Brunori, Ruggero, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Coates, Clive, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Iron Horse, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Hugh, 1991, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Zraly, Rosemary, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Oversize: Series III: Food Writers and Personalities
  - Brennan, Georgeanne, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Brown, Helen, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Costner, Susan, 1990/1991 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Cox, Beverly; Jacobs, Martin, April 6, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Damerow, Gail, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Devi, Yamuna, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Giobbi, Edward, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Gold, Rozanne, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Goldstein, Joyce, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Gotto, Antonio M, 1991, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Grigson, Sophie, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Harlow, Jay, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Hendra, Tony, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Hibler, Janie, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Horn, Jane, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Johnson, Peter, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Jones, Judith Ann, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Kafka, Barbara, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Klavan, Ellen, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Koplan, Steven, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Laube, James, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Lesem, Jeanne, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - London, Mel and Sheryl, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - McCullough, Frances, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Ortiz, Yvonne, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Pellegrini, Angelo, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Raichlen, Steven, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Rodgers, Rick, August 24, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Rozin, Elizabeth, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Ryan, Lawrence Timothy, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Sandison, Teri, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - Sass, Lorna J., 1992 (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Sax, Richard, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - Scott, Sally Anne, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - Stallworth, Lyn, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Stillman, Julie, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - Stone, Sally and Martin, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Tropp, Barbara, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 52)
  - Verde Barr, Nancy, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 53)
  - Weaver, William Woys, March 15, 2001, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 54)
  - Wells, Patricia, November 10, 1993, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 55)
- Oversize: Series IV: Miscellaneous
  - Australian Premium Wine Collection, November 6, 1996, January 13, 2001, [undated] (Box 59, Folder 56)